<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Chicago.PM</title>
        <link>http://chicago.pm.org/blog/tag/presentation/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://chicago.pm.org/blog/tag/presentation.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <description>Blog feed of Chicago.PM</description>
        <generator>Statocles 0.053</generator>
        <item>
            <title>Building Command-Line Applications: Doug Bell - May 23</title>
            <link>http://chicago.pm.org/blog/2013/05/20/building-command-line-applications-doug-bell-may-23.html</link>
            <guid>http://chicago.pm.org/blog/2013/05/20/building-command-line-applications-doug-bell-may-23.html</guid>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <p>This will be an intermediate-level presentation on how to build command-line applications in Perl. It starts out with some simple command-line scripts, and moves on to building testable, reusable command-line applications using modules and CPAN frameworks. Knowledge of Perl and using the command-line is recommended. Previous knowledge of writing command-line applications is not required.</p>

<p>Pizza and beverages will be provided (if you have requests for specific flavors of pizza or beverage, let me know). Please <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Windy-City-Perl-mongers-Meetup/events/119961772/">RSVP on the meetup page</a> before 4:00pm on Thursday to make your entrance as smooth as possible.</p>

<p>This will be the first in a set of free, open-source intermediate-level presentations released by the Chicago.PM organization on Github. The presentation itself will be released with a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike license, and the code inside the presentation will be licensed under the same terms as Perl itself (Artistic License 1 or GPL version 1 at your discretion). Our goal is to build a repository of living presentations that pick up after the beginner&#39;s workshops and explore single topics with some depth. Emphasis will be placed on best practices with pragmatism: Here&#39;s multiple ways to do it, here&#39;s why you might choose one way over another, here&#39;s some things you might see out in the wild and how to improve on them. Our github organization is located at <a href="http://github.com/ChicagoPM">http://github.com/ChicagoPM</a></p>

<p>More information is available on <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Windy-City-Perl-mongers-Meetup/events/119961772/">the meetup page</a>.</p>

<p>Update: <a href="http://chicago.pm.org/Command-Line-Apps">Slides are available on the Talks page</a></p>

                    <p><a href="http://chicago.pm.org/blog/2013/05/20/building-command-line-applications-doug-bell-may-23.html#section-2">Continue reading...</a></p>
                <p>Tags:
                    <a href="/blog/tag/presentation/">presentation</a>
                    <a href="/blog/tag/announcement/">announcement</a>
                    <a href="/blog/tag/command-line/">command line</a>
                </p>
            ]]></description>
            <pubDate>
                Mon, 20 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000
            </pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>

